Â (Sad music)
(Reneano.
(What is it?
(I have a question. Is this a good time?
(Yes.
(I can't go to bed early. What should I do?
Everyone has problems with that, even when they grow up.
So it can't be cured. That's all.
♪ (sad music playing)
(♪ Ending theme ♪)
This is a short version of Anochan Channel.
Anochan karuta
Let's play.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't say anything vulgar, or it'll come out too soon.
It'll come out soon.
Yes, sir.
And...
and
(Music)
I'm thankfully very popular with kids these days.
I want that channel to be
I want kids to watch it.
That's kind of the concept behind it, from the beginning.
Then, "and" - "and" please.
Yes.
What's that? This is...
It's "Dad's a thief.
He's a thief, isn't he?
You're the father.
It's a bit of a shock to see him like that.
But he's mischievous.
He's a little cute. It's a beautiful drawing.
I'd like to sell this karuta.
I'd like to have them all. It'd be fun.
I want to sell them.
Neneano, I have a question. Is this a good time?
Yes.
What's up, sister?
I always regret fighting with my sister. What should I do?
You don't have to do that if you're going to regret it.
I know.
But I'm happy to fight.
If we get into a real fight, a real bad mood, we don't say a word.
Okay. Thank you.
Now for the surprise.
Surprise?
Oh, my God, isn't this ridiculous?
Everyone imagines it.
Then let's do this.
Okay, um...
Insert first.
It's like the flames are really shaking in the wind.
That's one way to describe it.
Really?
Surprise, what's this?
This is...
Surprise.
It was on that channel, too.
The cake's gonna explode.
Surprise, surprise.
We're done here.
Now it's complete.
This is a surprise!
Amachan Channel, subscribe to our channel!
by H.